[music]
[музыка]
hello everyone a
всем привет
few days ago I challenged the Russian blogger alexander losevo to a
несколько дней назад я вызвал на
public blogging duel,
публичный блогерскую дуэль российского
who
блогера александра лосево который своих
propagandizes in his streams that russia
стримах пропагандирует что россия
attacked ukraine correctly, that ukraine
правильно напала на украину что украина
bombed the donbass there for 8 years and various tattoos of
там 8 лет бомбила донбасс и разную тату
Russian false propaganda method manuals,
российскую пропагандистскую брехливые
so
методе методичку так и
we can say with confidence that  now
можем с уверенностью сказать что теперь
Alexander can rename his
александру можно переименовать свой
channel, demolished the name Losev Lid to the
канал снес название лосев лиф на канал
Losev Drain channel, but because the very first day
лосев слив а потому что первый же день
he personally refused this
он лично он отказался от этого вызова
call, that is, he showed that he can
так то есть он показал что он может
communicate there with some alcoholics there
общаться там с каким-то алкоголиками там
with some
с какими-то
hard workers so them  to mix up the git with his
работягами так им замешать гита свои
things, to talk them up, but for a serious
вещи забалтывать их но на серьезный
substantive conversation on the facts with
предметный разговор по фактам с
bloggers of Ukraine, he cannot, so that
блогерами украины он не может так то
is, this is a very convenient position for these
есть это очень удобная позиция вот этих
Russian bloggers, so they can
российских блогеров так они могут
do their propaganda of the MSD to you
заниматься своим пропаганда мсд вам
like this until they talk to
таким так до тех пор пока не поговорят с
someone  clearly calm and in fact, and
кем-то четко спокойно и по факту и
that's how it was great to watch the know and
вот так было прекрасно наблюдать знать и
subscribers from  Russia rewrote different things
подписчики из россии разных вещей
when there used to be something there
переписали когда раньше было что-то там
with some peasants you are
с какими-то мужиками разговариваешь
talking you will come across uncle glory he will interrupt
попадется тебе дядя слава он прервет
format, if you weren’t torn to lose,
формат вот если ты на лосево не рвался
so you should have interrupted you, okay, I threw a
так ты должен тебя прервал окей я кинул
challenge to losevo Losev merged as merged
вызов лосево лосев слился как слился
equals it’s so funny even if
равен это так по смешного даже ведь если
a
бы
person really had such a
действительно у человека была такая
position, he was ready to have the rest of it if
позиция он готов был ее остаток если вот
these Russian bloggers are propagandists
эти российские блогеры они пропагандисты
on  they
на зарплате так или кто-то ним плате так
don’t allow two of them to pay a salary no no you
то двоим не разрешают нет нет ты вот
find yourself some fools there if you don’t
найди себе каких-то там дурачков если не
talk but with serious people who, in
говори а с серьезными людьми которые по
fact, can load you up no no no,
фактах могут загрузить тебя нет нет не
because this will undermine our
надо потому что это нам подорвёт нашу
propaganda and so  it was funny until when
пропаганду и так смешно было до когда
after that he refused a bunch of
после этого как он отказался куча
Russian bot in our
российский бот в нашей киса там нет лоси
kitty  if it’s in you and
слабенькая соперника вот если в тебе и
they began to list further there what is the
начали дальше там перечисляться в чем
strength of brother petya 1 so dachas, now if
сила братом петя 1 итак дач вот если бы
they got you two call on will
они тебе попали двоих вызове на будет
let the
давайте
audience there 5 1 so the audience is what is the
аудитория там 5 1 так аудитория в чем
strength brother evgeny let’s I’m ready
сила брат евгений давайте я готов с ними
for a
на
duel with them such a discussion so on the facts
дуэль такую дискуссию так по фактам
template phoned skype zoom in
шаблон созвонились skype зум в чем
anything to make it happen to know and that the
угодно чтобы случилось так знать и что
roulette accidentally cut someone off because
рулетка случайно кого-то оборвал потому
it happens for some reason such a gleb and
что бывает почему-то такое глеб и
according to the facts of the water they talked about who is right
по фактам воды поговорили кто прав
russia or ukraine tapov
россия или украина тапов
russian bloggers or a ukrainian house so
русские блогеры или украинский домик так
this is very, very important because  that now
это очень-очень важно потому что сейчас
millions of people are suffering because of
миллионы людей как страдает из-за вот
this Russian propaganda how they
этой российской пропаганды как они
are afraid of a meeting, so let me be the
боятся встречи поэтому давайте я готов 5
first to write to them with eugene
первым так с евгением пишите им 2 тишь
also, by the way, if there are any
также да кстати если есть какие-то
Russian bloggers who are
российские блогеры которые
ready to challenge me there, so I
готовые там мне сделать вызов так я
agree, let's write to me there in the
соглашусь давайте пишите там мне в
comments or do your own
комментариях или так делайте свой
there is a public challenge so much there I
публичным вызов так сильно есть там
watched bloggers from the territory
смотрел блогеры с территории
occupied there Andrey Gorle with her
оккупированы там андрей горле с ее годам
husky years some give let's guys
хаски какие-то давать давайте пацаны
meet on and clearly on the facts we
встретимся на и четко по фактам разберем
will analyze who is cheating and that nonsense it will be
кто обман и то брехло это будет
interesting and
интересно и
you know I will specially read the
знаете я вот специально почитаю
comment under this post is
комментарий под этим постом это
it’s a separate pleasure to read how people
отдельное наслаждение читать как люди
react to this possible duel and
реагируют на вот эту возможную дуэль и
to the drain and duel, so here’s a comment
на слив и дуэли так вот комментарий
someone writes zoo alexander lost
кто-то пишет zoo александр лосев
handsome but there is a fan of losevo then
красавчик но там фанат лосево то
alexander and andrey it will be epic
александр и андрей это будет эпично
pretentious losev hello from penza no
пафосный лосев привет из пензы нет
someone from russia wants  wants a fight so
кто-то из россии хочет хочет боя так
Sergey Gribkovski is interesting of course, but
сергей грибковски интересно конечно но
for 99 percent of the plaid from the game of ice,
за с 99 процентов плед из игра льда он
he got scared, he turned out to be a coward
испугался он оказался трусом
, he can change his mind,
можно он передумывать возможны в этом
moderators or curators from the FSB or
модераторы или кураторы из фсб или кто
whoever is above him will still give him a
там над ним стоит все-таки дадут ему
conversation, so Grigory writes to talk to
разговор так григорий пишет поговорить
Eugene channel  what is the power to sell,
евгением канал в чем сила продавать
let's talk to evgeny
давайте евгений поговорим
so vladimir writes andryusha you yourself
так владимир пишет андрюша ты сама
don't work with would or try  xia
никакого работаешь с бы или стараются
rup maz from of course we pray from
руп маз от конечно мы намаз от
strike I write from the Russians and he
strike пишет я с россиян и он походу
seems to be pissed off it would be interesting to look at
зассал было бы интересно посмотреть на
this dialogue on the facts it’s a pity that he
данный диалог по фактам жаль что он
merged
слился
so the one who says a lot is not
так тот кто говорит много не андрей
andrey  the feast is ticking and who and the
украинец и тикает пир побачим а кто и
cat you will be until the Russian bloggers
котика ты будут до российские блогеры
turned out to be cowards yes it turns out
оказались трусами да получается
so
так
rub are looking for and I think that you are like
rub ищут а я считаю что вы типа про меня
deceiving people about me I fully
обманываете людей я полностью
support the special operation you are a liar
поддерживает спецоперацию вы брехун
let's talk rainbow on video artem andrey is
давайте радуга на видос поговорим
so paid that he
артем андрей настолько проплачен что он
himself laughs in the evenings  about the fact that he
сам смеяться по вечерам о том что он
says the wolf, perhaps
говорит волк возможно
having signed a guest, only for some reason he didn’t
подписав гостях у только почему-то не
post a conversation with you, but well, it’s clear
выложил разговор с вами но ну понятно
why, in principle, keep
почему в принципе так держать давите
it up, press the lesson, too, it was a greyhound mess, screwed up,
урок тоже был борзый бардак облажался
so there is a channel, what is the power of brother, talk
так есть канал в чем сила брат поговори
to him to give give and brother everything is ready  yes,
с ним давать давать и брата все готов да
the classic is bombarded with bloggers, it doesn’t pull,
the classic засыпан блогерами не тянет
he was already scared by David, sweetheart, he
он уже испугался давидом
writes, I really want to see
мила ласки напишет очень хочется глянуть
how he rolls you out, but  lexander desirable and
как вас раскатает александр желательно и
desirable vladimir north stream 3
желательно владимир северный поток 3
alexander hasn’t rolled out already alexander has already
александр уже не раскатал александр уже
refused to
отказался от
roll out so much to his liking why did he
раскатки так по душе почему это он как
seem to understand that you would not be interested in
бы понял что вам это будет неинтересно
north stream 3 by the way they added a
северный поток 3 там кстати дописали
strong stream 3 with steps to give them to
шагами сильный поток 3 давать им на
north stream 3 we can talk and
северный поток 3 можем поговорить и
northern stream 3 if he is brave so
северным потоком 3 если он смелый так
kharkov writes very interesting
харьков пишет очень интересно
so evgeniy writes losev you bend so badly
так евгений пишем лосев ты так плохо
130 first I doubt that he
гнётся 130 первых сомневаюсь что вообще
will appear in the second there will be nothing to trump
появится в вторых нечем будет козырять
so it turned out yes
так и получилось да
both lists he will be preparing for a duel for half a year you
оба списка он полгода будет готовиться к
probably understand what’s the matter that
дуэли наверно понимаете в чем дело что
people are dying  now it’s like this in
люди умирают сейчас так быть через
six months, now it’s already and therefore it’s
полгода вот сейчас уже и поэтому это
very important these Russian bloggers
очень важно вот эти российские блогеры
are deceiving people to deceive on a huge
они обманывают людей обмануть в огромных
scale their own Russian
масштабах своей же российских так людей
people so that they can tell them
для того чтобы им скажем забалтывать
why they need to kill people in Ukraine, so
почему нужно убивать людей в украине так
okay, they were fooled there in the first
ладно были оболванены там в первые
weeks already  boots, everything is already clear to everyone,
недели уже сапогах уже всем все стает
but in order to
понятно но для того чтобы не было вот
avoid these  thieves in the middle of russia
этих разговоров середине россии на
why why are we bombing people in ukraine
почему почему мы бомбим людей в украине
so they will chatter that this is how it
так они вот заболтают том что это так и
should be so further on
надо итак дальше на
here writes diana challenge evgeny to a duel
вот пишет диана вызови на дуэль евгения
for evgeny there are a lot of top before watched
за евгении очень много топе до смотрел
his video before a very high
его видео до очень такой качественный
-quality propagandist can be seen that the former military before
пропагандист видно что военный бывший до
I’m ready to fight with him so according to the facts
с ним готов сразиться так по фактам
absolutely it’s
абсолютно это так
so writes on I’ll put varnishes on all these
так пишет на поставлю лаки по всем этим
videos if you speak honestly with Eugene about the
видео если с евгением будешь говорить по
facts, you
фактами честно ты же вроде фактами и
like to talk about facts and dates, and yes, Eugene is one of
датами любишь говорить и да евгений из
those people who check all the
тех людей которые проверяют всю инфу
dubious information immediately on the air  that is,
сомнительную сразу же в эфире то есть
it won’t work to lie, I’ll order it’s super, I’m
врать не получится велю это же супер я
ready from me just such an
готов от меня как раз такой
interlocutor such an
собеседник такой
opponent is very interesting, but
противник очень интересен а потому что
because if I’m not ready
вот если я не убеждения готовы их
to defend my beliefs, if people are not ready to
отстаивать так если люди не готовы
defend their beliefs if
отстаивать свои убеждения если не
they’re not paid, that’s why they don’t want
проплаченный так поэтому они не хотят
to go out on  such a duel so does she write
выходить на такие дуэль так ли она пишет
Kalinina not a hookah well done andrey
калинина не кальяне молодец андрей
so
так
someone writes alexander handsome but
кто-то пишет александр красавчик но
alexander scared
александр ведь испугался нам
when the broadcast
denis полуянов пышет когда трансляция
will be broadcast please let me know, I’m
будет сообщите пожалуйста я с российской
not very interested in listening and
стороны не очень интересно послушать и
finding out the truth from the Russian side, finally,
узнать правду наконец-то все испугался
your Russian blogger was scared of everything like this,
ваш российский блогер типа так раз
and he won’t be with him if he
ляться и с ним не будет если он где-то
doesn’t decide somewhere,
не надумает так
so bravo, I
так браво бой
support the fight  wrestling writes for one hundred
поддерживаю рестлинг пишет за сто
percent because he understands Andreev
процентов потому что понимает андреева
hello from I was already so scared the
привет от испугался уже
bill for Evgeny then Stanislav
счет за евгения то тогда станислав
Lesnevsky also check the channel what is the strength
лесневский еще чекните канал в чем сила
brother
брат
this will be the top cantante waiting for such an
это это будет топ cantante жду такой
issue worthy opponents again
выпуск достойные оппоненты вновь слился
merged that opponent merged
вот тот оппонент слился
so I look forward to good luck  we are
так жду с нетерпением желаю удачи на
looking forward to the previous ones, although they
прежние ждем с нетерпением хотя снова же
will again yell and fix it, I sincerely wish
будут орать и закрепить искренне желаю
you good luck don’t look with moose why I
вам удачи не смотрите с лосевым почему я
chose him so it seems to me that
его выбрал так мне кажется что с ним
you can build a dialogue with him without screaming so yes
можно построить диалог без криков так да
he can chatter he has
он может забалтывать вот есть у него
one but at least this  this is not a
такой но по крайней мере это не это
blogger who is grimacing there swearing
блогер который там кривляется матюкаться
there screaming with him it would be possible to build an
там кричит с ним можно было бы построить
interesting one, that is, I did it
интересный делал то есть я его
considered as a worthy opponent,
рассматривал как достойного соперника
well, he merged refused
ну он слился отказался
[music]
[музыка]
so I write Andrey I think you should not
так пишет я андрей считаю вам не стоит с
communicate with this Losev Alex writes Losev
этим лосевым общаться алекс пишет лосев
obviously disagree with that person, at least
явно не согласиться ту человеку хоть
more or less with some kind of intellect, everything
более менее каким-то интеллектом все
clearly disagreed Yes you were right
понятно не согласился да вы были правы
tata
tata
daddy basics for  troit ukraine is not ukraine,
папик основы за троит украина не украина
well, if a person calls my
ну если человек будет обзывать мою
country names he was england, respectively,
страну был англии соответственно
so under them don’t be a disgrace, you’re not up
так под их не позорься ты не дотягиваешь
to it, you see, get glasses so
далось вы видите получить очки так
alcoholics there are youngsters there, I’m not
алкоголики там малолетки там работе я не
up to the moose ones, but the good thing is that the pub did
дотягиваю до лосиков а вот блага паб это
n’t reach you yourself, it’s not funny
не дотянул до вам самим не смешно
excuse before
отмазка до
and
а
what will change the same ordinary Russian
чего изменит это же обычный российский
pus behind the synthesizer he deliberately
гной за синтезатором он сознательно
drives this vile woola yes I think that
гонят эту мерзкую woola да я считаю что
he deliberately does it so I
он сознательно это делает так у меня
had some doubts about the possible being
были некоторые сомнения возможного
mistaken so but after he
заблуждается так но после того как он
refused it is clear that he is doing this
отказался ясно что он делает это
purposefully
целенаправленно
saint anton writes  daddy got pissed off
святой антоне пишет папик обгадился два
twice decided their 3rd sleigh don't communicate with
раза решил их 3 саня не общайся с
flawed sorry
ущербными пожалей сальный решил пожалеть
if the
если усах
mustache decided to promote itself at the expense of the moose
так решил попиариться за счет лосево
, the excuse is so good, I’m for the video, you’re
так хорош отмазка я за ролик к лычко ты
primitive, and I’m on the air all the soul 8
примитивным а я прямого эфира все душа 8
so you can open cartoons with latitudes
так вы мультики может широтами открывать
and stars without facts, my thought is that the
и звездицы без фактов моя думка что и
moose is from the cycle and cashing in on the
лось из цикла и на нажиться на
d-orbital  socks, his mind, let’s increase the
d-орбиталь носки его разум приумножим
given lawn mower
дан бензокоса
, he’ll be glad to al bullock account on
именно порадуется ал буллок аккаунт на
this way and that,
так и так
I also thought that he would ripen who
подать я тоже думал что бы поспел кого
you are the most standing favorite capital from there,
ты самый стоя любимый капиталов оттуда
from his videos Winx, many conclusions are
из своих видео винкс много выводов свои
sad so that the mats don’t look so bad
грустно чтобы не таким дурным маты
for his audience,
выглядит для своей аудитории
sergey puzzles writes something  otherwise, he won’t accept the
сергей пазлы пишет то не то не примет он
challenge, all the more so on the air, he all
вызов тем более в прямом эфире все он
merged clearly, maybe we can get
слился на видно можем может нам можно ни
scared there, like when a set-up
там перепугались типа когда подстава
like parts of the
типа части по
hat come out, maybe he’ll change his mind, but it’s
шапке выйдут может еще передумает но
unlikely that is, if a person
навряд ли то есть если человек у него
has understanding in his soul and in his heart  that he is
есть в душе и в сердце понимание что он
right he is ready to prove it to anyone I am ready
прав он готов это доказать любом я готов
to meet with any Russian bloggers
с любым российским блогерам у так
and
встретиться да и
find out by facts who is right who is wrong
выяснить по фактам кто прав кто не прав
if the Russian blogger of this  to be afraid, well,
если российский блогер этого бояться ну
that’s understandable, then it’s true,
значит вот понятно затем правда
so Andrey Kraschiy Andrey Fedorov writes,
так андрей кращий андрей федоров пишет
call Evgeny, they’re elk to get
вызываете евгении они лося на добраться
to the real summer of Russian bloggers, why, Evgeny,
до он настоящий лета русских блоггеров
let’s call you too,
чё евгений давайте вызываем вас тоже
if you need a separate call, we’ll write down if the
если надо отдельный вызов запишем если
people who are watching Evgeny there are all their
люди которые там смотрят евгения всю им
strength, brother, write ready to organize with
силы брат пишите готовы организовать с
the duel was very interesting for him,
ним дуэль это очень интересно был
and
а
Andrey Losev was not at all equal to you,
андрей лосев совсем вам не равнялась
terribly leads dialogues, turns off the sound,
ужасно ведет диалоги выключает звук
plays the piano and, in fact,
играет на пианино и по факту сказать
can’t say anything worse than Uncle Glory
ничего не может то хуже дяди славы
that you smashed the tanks and the blade to,
которую вы разнесли tanks и клинка до
as I think that yes, I saw that he was there the
как я считаю что да я видел что он там
difference  with people there oink cinnamon playing on
разница с людей там хрю корицу играя на
but I think that it is possible to build a dialogue
но я считаю что можно построить диалог
worthy of the facts so without these there
достойным по фактам так без вот этих там
shout insults at her so but he sees
выкрикните в ней оскорблений так но он
frightened
видите испугался
Victoria writes to you this little will start
виктория пишет тебе этого мало начнет
reading you training manuals this is
зачитывать тебе методички это
professional propaganda 0 baht all the
профессиональный пропаганда 0 бат все
money on the grief of people  so look
деньги на горе людей так смотрите
Victoria it is necessary why, because up to a
виктория надо почему потому что до очень
lot of those with whom we communicate earn money
много тех с кем мы общаемся зарабатывает
for a year of these manuals, they don’t sound like they’re
на год этих методичка hе звучат они
narrative Russian promote like this, but
narrative российские продвигают так но с
you need to work with them, you need to show that
ними надо работать надо показывать что
they are wrong, and you need to smash them not and
они неправы так и надо разбивать их не и
manuals, but
методички а
into smithereens,
в дребезги
you’ll be in the paws of short-term
будете к лапы short-term
Evgenia Sivtsova writes, I saw how you
евгения сивцова пишет видела я как ты
stream and worry  ten times
ведешь стрим и переживаешь по десять раз
the same question asking hitech when a
одно и то же спрашивающий hitech когда
bug what kind of battle do you
жучок какой тебе баттл
need and timur kulbaka enters into communicate with the
да тимур кульбака впишет в общайся с
northern one under current 3 you definitely won’t take
северным под током 3 ты его точно не
him out ready with a strong stream 3
вывезешь давать готов сильным потоком 3
write to him timur kurbakov is ready for a battle
пишите ему тимур курбаков готов на баттл
with him
с ним
so andrey is beautiful so it becomes
так андрей красава так это становится
interesting
интересным
dika you directly owe to daddy won
дику вам прямо обязана на папик победил
the duel better with evgeny channel what is the
в дуэль лучше с евгением канал в чем
strength of brother or weak no not weak let's
сила брат или слабо нет не слабо давайте
so andrey even gave a trick try you
так андрей даже дал хитрость пробую вы
really here and put the merged
правда вот и ставим же слился
rodeo writes you a typical talker
родео пишет вам типичный болтун
constantly interrupt you don't know how to conduct a
постоянно перебивайте не умеете вести
dialogue boring interesting  don’t look
диалог скучно интересно не смотрите
like if bored olga shalyapina puffs up
вроде если скучно ольга шаляпина пышет
writes losev in a cool voice in merged he
пишет лосев крутой голосе в слился он
turned out to be not cool connected
оказался не крутое подключены
so is the bath  I litvinenko writes that they saw
так и ванная литвиненко пишет видели
this Losevo, this is a really paid
этого лосево это реально проплаченный
type, so the fourth option is one hundred
тип так что четвертый вариант сто
percent and the most disgusting to observe the
процентов и самая противная наблюдать
psychological techniques of the country’s forces, which
психологические приемы сил страны что
says special training, I thought that she
говорит спецподготовки подумал что у нее
has some kind of special training, that is,
есть кое-то спецподготовка так то есть
it seems to me that it’s just a person who
мне кажется просто человек так вот ведет
behaves like this, it’s
себя то
interesting like that  what is the name of the channel for
интересно так как канал называется у
this Losevo on the channel is called Losev
этого лосево на канал называется лосев
drain
слив
so Losevo kaput he works for the FSB
так лосево капут он работает на фсб
Losev for shame True, one has already
лосев за стыд правда одна уже много
succeeded a lot because of the well-fed uniquely shy
удалось из-за сыт однозначно пугливые
beast No need for surnames Go on a
зверь не надо на фамилий переходите
good move to get high due to a more
хороший ход кайфануть за счет более
popular blogger, this is every second one
популярного блогера это каждый второй
there will be no way to challenge us to a duel,
может пути нам вызвать на дуэль будет не
if bloggers
смотрите если
show that they ruined the
показывает что они развалили тут
Ukrainians here like nuts, so finding some
украинцев как орешки так находя каких-то
random people, let's try to
случайных людей давайте мы попробуем
really communicate with a tough nut
реально с крепким орешком пообщаться так
and see what the nuts are stronger than
и посмотреть че и орешки крепче ра
the
то
number is stitched the main feature of
номер прошит основная фишка
manipulating moose  drain I will
манипулирования лосев слив я буду так
call all the facts the
называть все факты собеседник его
interlocutor calls him  they use personal opinions and fictions, and
называют личным мнением и выдумками а
his propaganda theses are indisputable
его пойти тезисы пропаганды неоспоримыми
facts, and if the interlocutor develops a
фактами да если собеседник развивать
topic in order to bring him to
тему для того чтобы вывести его на
clean water, he abruptly switches and again
чистую воду он резко переключать и снова
disperses fakes on superficial topics,
разгоняет фейки на поверхностные темы
that’s why he was scared of Andrei
вот видно поэтому он испугался на андрей
Lvov writes me coins and the task of wine is on
львов пишет мне монеток а задача вин на
kind of story so class bored andreev's
вид повесть так класса бородай андреева
music into eternity and good luck in smearing it
музыка в вечность и удачи в размазывания
from the nobility with her you blurry horns
из знати него нею с их вы рожек blurry
so I yazh yes but this metal is visible
так я яж да но это металл видно илья
Ilya Yashin who writes but this is already
яшин который пишет а вот это уже
interesting the duel is strong yes it
интересно дуэли это сильно да это очень
seems very good to me it is very good  the format is so
мне кажется это очень хороший формат так
when it’s not just here we find some
когда не просто вот мы находим каких-то
incomprehensible people there suck who is wrong or
непонятных людей там соси кто не так или
they find from ukraine and let’s fight
они находят из украины а давайте битва
on equal terms blogger from blogger this is a very
на равных блогер из блогера это очень
good format people want to understand then after
хороший формат люди хотят понять затем
all it’s true so if Russian
все-таки правда так если российские
bloggers run away from this  then everything
блогеры убегают от этого то тогда все
becomes very obvious,
становится очень очевидно
so I have seen everything in my life with the name daddy, of
так я все в жизни видел на фамилию папик
course, it’s not a daddy’s frenzy, but an attempt, if
это конечно угар не папик а попытка если
in Russian, then daddy  rmalally, the surname is a
по-русски то папы нормально фамилия
derivative of the profession, that is, there was
производная от профессии то есть был
someone in the priest row, that is, a priest in
кто-то в ряду священник то есть поп в
tsarist Russia, it was called pop, so
царской россии это называлось поп так у
from this and from these things in other
и от этого и в этих вещей в других
languages, too, and that is, from this it
языках тоже вот и то есть от этого и
went like a forger there kovalenko and  so
пошло как там коваль там kovalenko и так
on,
дальше
since he would have climbed into Dublin’s
как он забрался бы дублина
soup and writes that it’s not so at Alexander’s that you
суп и пишет что не так у александра вы
have been mistaken for a long time, you got lost there,
давно уже заблуждайтесь заблудились там
everything is miserable full under and well, you see
все убогий полной под и ну вот видите на
what you are Alexandra Alexander
что вы такое александра александр не
cannot be responsible for his words, and so he
может отвечать за свои слова а так он
runs away from this
убегает от этого
Alexei Gashek  writes like this, losev just
алексей гашек пишет так лосев только
started to be a genius for you, what is the strength of the
начал вам быть гением сели в чем сила
brother or the northern stream, it was interesting there,
брат или северный поток вот там было
but I just started if you
интересно таки я только начала если
look, I’ve only been doing this for half a year after the
смотреть я только полгода после
active invasion of the Russian
активного вторжения российской федерации
Federation, but I’m ready from let’s go to the
этим занимаюсь но я готов из давайте
northern streams evgeny if you all
северной потоки евгений если вы все
believe that your  these bloggers are idols
верите что ваши эти блогеры кумиры
ready to fight so come on I'm ready to wait
готовы сражаться так давайте я готов жду
so
так
katya stuffed magnificently screw the wedding
катя набила пышно винт венчальный
propagandist about these facts and
пропагандист про эти факты и много
they talk a lot in moscovy before capturing  the cabin
говорят в московию до захватывать кабину
from the 2014 lesson the goal is a fact than but you can
с 2014 урока цель факт чем но можно
tell about and addressing you then
сказать об и вам адресации вы тогда
Aibar Tulebaev writes finally someone will
айбар тулебаев пишет наконец-то кто-то
put the elk in place until we see it
поставит лосево на место до видим его
was already set as a goal he called because
поставили уже целью он вызвал потому что
he merged was
он слился
frightened of a serious conversation
испугался серьезного разговора
you know how the kids in the alley
вы знаете как малышей в подворотне
offend and when I met they delivered
обижать а когда встретился доставили
to save her no mom called
сохранить у нее нет мама позвонила
look at the potatoes like interfere for a long time
смотрите на картошку типа помешать долго
karla successfully where you do the facts I'm
карла успешно где вы делаете фактами я
from monterrey on your side so the truth is
из монтеррея на вашей стороне так правда
on the side of ukraine
на стороне украины
so at the groats of england you under the bike
так у крупу англии вам под байка
in 1333 writes andrey the disk can be lost with
в 1333 пишет андрей диск терять можно с
people  good or bad people with
людьми хорошими или плохими людьми с по
risk even we will not
рискнут даже мы будем обзывания не буду
read names, so andrey respect you to
зачитывать так андрей уважение вам
tell the camp so
сказать станом так
you are for a visa and please go to the duel of the
виза вы за и пожалуйста на дуэль блогера
blogger what is the strength of brother doom it
в чем сила брат doom это действительно
will really be important already said yes so why
будет важном уже говорили да так зачем
let it hurt yourself glory to ukraine  and
пускай было болит у себя слава украине и
so what's the point of having a dialogue with
так какой смысл вести диалог с
propagandists who wanted to figure it out
пропагандистами кто хотел разобраться
figured out no need to conduct I think that
разобрался нет надо вести я считаю что
it is necessary to  show that they are deceivers
надо надо показывать что они обманщики
or let them show that we are deceivers
или пусть они покажут что мы обманщики
and
а
come with me to such a queen maybe you
иди со мной к такие queen может быть ты
would pick up the motive was active mom them
бы забрать был мотив активный маме них
why not refuse with a moose
не почему не откажется с лосем могла бы
could if we agreed that
вот если бы мы договорились о том что мы
we do not lead a whale
не ведем кита
name-calling there  calling each other's countries
обзывание там обзывание стран друг друга
there horns Ukraine so further I think
там рожки украиной так дальше я думаю
that it would be possible to build a
что можно было бы построить
normal dialogue
нормальный диалог
I think this is lacking in the Ukrainian and
мне кажется этого в украинской и в
Ukrainian and Russian blogosphere
украинской и российской блогосфере не
so they don’t give a damn about the truth scrape their own
так им наплевать на правду скрести свое
repeats a hundred for the sake of repeated nonsense
повторяется сто ради повторено брехня
so
так
eric y more with flow two  of a variant of
эрик y больше с потоком два варианта
Russian flea rhymes, they call both
российских блох рифмы обзывается оба
continue in NATO in the cold, they didn’t get married, they
продолжить в нато на морозе не венчаны
turned on themselves and the fool to the chair, he
стала себе включат и дурня к стул он
writes to crumble, you’re not afraid of plump
пишет посыпаться не боишься пухляш ты с
people, you don’t take it out with ordinary people, you see,
обычными людьми то не вывозишь вы видите
yes, your login fell down
да посыпался ваш логин
the so-called Russian bloggers in
все так называемые русские блогеры в
roulette ordinary high fires in the war people
рулетке обычные хай пожары на войне люди
without conscience and honor many of them
без совести и чести многие из них
perfectly understand the current  realities but in
прекрасно понимают нынешние реалии но на
truth you won’t earn a lot of money on a
правде много денег не заработаешь на
zombie cheers-patriots purely business nothing
зомбака ура-патриоты чисто бизнес ничего
personal to maybe with people without
личного к может быть до с людьми без
conscience and honor trying to prove anything
совести и чести пытаться что-либо
to them is like throwing pearls
доказать им все равно что метать бисер
in front of pigs
перед свиньями
yes so
да так
Volodya more I know how the wine
володя больше я знаю чем закончится вин
will end  sukkot still screaming often
будет суккот еще из кричат often
taf-taf-taf not and xy pade me oh he ran away
тяф-тяф-тяф не и xy пэде мне о он убежал
even before the start of the special operation the
еще до начала начала спецоперации
answer to those places from the operation and so
ответ на тех мест с операции и так пишет
he writes he won’t go for it he understands everything perfectly
он не пойдет на это он же все прекрасно
yes he didn’t go he understood everything perfectly
понимает да он ни пошёл он все прекрасно
gallery writes this is a very cool idea, but
gallery пишет это очень крутая идея но
this 8 is clearly paid propagandists,
этот 8 явно проплаченный пропагандисты
so he immediately ran away, he sees a
поэтому сразу же убежал он видит
strong opponent who is oriented
сильного оппонента который ориентируется
in the dates of history, he is engaged in a dialogue of an
в датах истории ведет диалог
intellectual and we are not profitable such
интеллигента и мы не выгодно такое
communication if the diablo challenge would
общение если бы diablo вызов то будет
always evade, put pressure on the emotions of the
вечно увиливать давить на эмоции
audience, constantly interrupts confusingly
зрителей постоянно перебивает с толку
so that the viewer could not hear you andrey
чтобы зритель не смог слышать вас андрей
vlad vyazemsky call for a conversation
влад вяземский вызовите на разговор
then please the collective farm is a
потом пожалуйста колхоз дело
voluntary matter not how old the cattle is
добровольное не насколько [__] лет
white  cotton is not good, and those who
беловатым не годится есть и те которые
called there, for example, evgeny, what is the strength of the
называли там например евгений в чем сила
gate, it seems to me that it would be more worthy with him,
ворот мне кажется с ним было бы более
but if the collective farm wants to make a
достойно но если колхоз хочет сделать не
challenge, I will accept him,
вызов я его приму
let's talk so this
давайте поговорим так этот фиде раз не
fide will not come out for a duel, he will [ __ ] himself glory to
выйдет на дуэль он обосрётся слава
Ukraine so talk son  gringoire
украине так пообщайся сын гренгуар
human yes andrey arlovsky if you
людским да андрей арловский если ты меня
hear me yes you are very interesting
слышишь да ты очень интересный
propagandists from the throat
пропагандисты из горловки
I am ready to fight with you
я готов с тобой сразиться
so what are the tongues and
так какое космы языки и
so
так
we
у
still have such a plaster they are from Florida
есть еще такой гипс они из флориды
so I bet that it will freeze before the
так ставлю ставку что застыть до игр
games for the queen
будет за queen застал
and I check a  here the horror is disheartening and we
а я чекаю а вот ужас унываешь и мы
jump out of mercy above and rhino sweetie yes
выскочить милости выше и rhino лапчик да
rhino immune instead of
по ней rhino иммунный вместо чего
courage
смелости
so bear veremchuk writes about such an
так мишка веремчук пишет о прям такая
intrigue shark from there was a bear khabib and
интригой акула из было мишка хабиб и
mcgregor I don’t know what was there and khabib
макгрегор не знаю что там и хабибом
played wounds here unleashed very quickly
играли раны тут развязалась очень быстро
so he merged
так он слился
like that
так
the shaft of police officers writes he is not of your level
вал исправников пишет он не твой уровень
did not get out take someone simpler
не вывелись его бери кого-нибудь попроще
something he decided that he would not take him out and he
что-то он решил что он не вывезет и он
fell off 1
отвалился 1
yes
да
regina is he  he is not in a hurry to treat
регина ли он не спешит угостила факты
you with specific facts for insults and lies
конкретика у вас на оскорбления и ложь
he is not your level take someone
он не ваш уровень возьмите кого-то
simpler otherwise you can embarrass yourself lady
попроще а то можете опозориться леди на
I was ready to be disgraced ready to disgrace myself in a fair
я готов был опозориться готов в честном
fight but for some reason your blogger
бою опозориться но почему-то ваш блогер
he got scared and merged
он испугался и слился
varnish
лак
blue shevchenko donuts juices  the level for
синяя шевченко пышек соки уровень для
him, of course, mario landers, the strike
него конечно же марио landers стачку
will be like this, but this is the truth, the truth
будет такого но такова правда правда
is called andrey, the truth is behind us, ukraine
зовут андрей правда за нами украина
will win
победит avr аховая пишет я думаю что он
he didn’t go to the duel he was scared or we
он не пошел на дуэль он испугался или мы
didn’t allow it there
там не разрешили
I hope the manure
надеюсь навоз
patrick topic is ready I don’t know what it means
патрик topic готова не знаю что означает
like until melted so the
типе до талого так
phrases
фразам
marina caravan sk caravan skype I’m waiting for
марина караван ск караван skype жду-жду
andrey you jump him and but we tore
андрей вы его прыгать и но мы оторвали
off at the stage of challenges the share he is susanna
еще на этапе вызовов долю он сусанна
magic  rubber pasha block you're afraid of this and
магия каучук паша блока побоишься это и
you think wine on pidan attacks cro queen
думаешь вин на пидан атаки кро queen
good know my nonsense I'll put
добрый знаю свои брехню я помещу за нею
three mines miller puppies behind her you need to levin for
три мины миллер щенята с вами надо левин
sure  I’ll be broken think wine just about
точно буду разбитый думай вин просто про
ignore let’s try it he was scared of us
игнор испробуем это он испугался нам
hovering Rusov writes
парит русов пишет
with a call Evgeny from St. Petersburg let’s
с вызове евгений из питера давайте
Evgeny I’m ready all Evgeny
евгений я готов все фанаты евгения
’s fans let’s write ready to do with him
давайте пишите готовы сделать с ним
I say
говорю
so
так
I’m like a ball writes he will never
вот я как шарик пишет он никогда не
go for it he’s a smart person not  he knows
пойдет на это он умный человек не знает
that his country and he is not right, does he, like
что его страна и он не прав ли он как
Putin, know how and where they will leave their
путин знает как и где оставят свои
interests so Vitaly Tkachuk the oregano of
интересы так виталий ткачук душицы
colleagues that we will take it off and although he and all the
коллег что примем выкл и хотя он и
same Slovaks da-ming was afraid of the forest
всетаки словаки да-мин забоялся из леса
so for a vessel of the hour and I don’t like c
так на сосуд часу а я не люблю c
Russian propagandist  show me
российского пропагандиста покажите мне
his place of the
его месте
Artyom spirit tear it up the truth behind
артемовского духа порви его правда за
us sho there it can scare the patron
нами шо оно там может попугать патрон
writes he will never agree
пишет никогда он не согласится
so here and already here
так вот и уже здесь
maxim priests will write good evening
отпишет максим попов добрый вечер
specially mad language of the dome so that
специально бешенный языке купола чтобы
it is clear for future bots that
было понятно для будущих ботов которые
most likely I will run here rule
скорее всего я сюда набегут правило
a bold proposal, most likely from his
смелое предложение на скорее всего с его
side, he will hate the broth so and the Armenians
стороны будет хейти бульон так и армян
so it would be cool the throne stands from so
так было бы круто трон за стоит от так
he merged chi sho yes merged  I’m
он слился чи шо да слился
such a cool format no drain and
так крутой формат никакие слива и
mute in the chat roulette handsome
отключение звука в чат-рулетке красавчик
but it’s
но это
yes I need to put it in its place
да меня его надо поставить на место
hi becoming shall write cool in any way it
хай став shall пишет круто по-любому
will refuse because on the side of Ukraine it’s really
откажется ведь на стороне украины правда
easier for us and it turned out you were
нам проще да так и получилось вы были
right  I’d
права он отказался испугался как бы
hide
скрываю
Yuri the authorities flashing it’s pointless to
юрий власти вспыша это бессмысленно
tell why it won’t work like this
рассказывать почему не пойдет таким
pancakes you really
получилось блинчики вы реально вот
see it will be
видите найти пропагандистов будет
interesting to find propagandists so it’s
интересно так
like looking for where you can compete with an elk
вроде ищет куда тебе с лосем тягаться
if you just merge the
если так сольешь только записки не
notes don’t forget to see the
забудь посмотрим рода все нет записи
kind  this is all the salinity, with
запретили а вот это вся соленость вот
this toy, the benefit of sadaka in circles
этой игрушкой блага садака кружками
will soon be the army of the world and everything is like
скоро армия мира и все так саммиту
that, something to ruin and lay out for the summit, but
что-то там разваливать и выкладывать а
they can’t go out to a fair fight, but the
на честный бой выйти они не могут а вот
guys from Russia, what’s up with the face of the
ребята из россии что там как с лицом
matter,
дела
daddy most likely waved
папик вперед размахивала скорее всего
this moose forward  killer they are all cowardly and
этот лосев убийца они все трусливые да
so they get
так и получают
so
так
damask steel writes I am waiting for mahacha a good show
булат пишет у жду махача хорошее шоу
will all not find
будет все не нашел
ro  ma lillian above stopudovo flashed the
рома лиллиан выше стопудово засветил
supreme knowing the percentage
верховный зная процент
so the
так
blood writes talk to the guy from the
кровь пишет поговорите с парнем с канала
loop channel 1 very competently literate it
петель 1 очень грамотно грамотный было
would be interesting it would be interesting the
бы интересно было бы интересным сам
Ukrainian himself comes from ukraine so it would be
украинец родом из украины так было бы
interesting to talk to him let's sing
интересно с ним поговорить давайте петь
about 1 if you are not like Losev so  like
о 1 если вы не такой как лосев так типа
if you are braver we can make a fight so
если вы посмелее можем сделать бой так
georgi appeared 50 it will be a bomb if
георги появился 50 это будет бомба если
no moose will collapse andrey it is black
лосем нет рухнут андрей это черная
against white truth inside the country light
против белого правда внутри стране свет
to defeat him thanks
победить ему спасибо георгий
to george in one ibragimov writes popik call
в один ибрагимов пишет попик вызове
vovazilvova your business will be vovazilvova
vovazilvova ваши дела будут vovazilvova
call you yours if there are subscribers
вызываю тебя твой если есть подписчики
vovazilvova let's  we are still
vovazilvova давайте мы сейчас вот еще
there in the comments someone writes Vova
там в комментах кто то пишет вова
Donbassky he is well aware of how and what
донбасский ему хорошо известна как и что
happened Mr. Popper will make him like a child
было мистера поппера сделает как ребенка
and even patrols properly let's
да еще и патрули как следует давайте
guys who are his subscribers you are from
ребята кто там подписчики его вы со
Lviv so let me be ready to fight with him
львова так давайте я готов с ним на
otherwise it will be  how with stupid Turks glory to
то будет как с тупым туркам слава
ukraine on ahaha propagandist is a
украине на ахаха пропагандист является
factor in holy water rocker
фактор в качельки святой воды
tooth  I give Svetlana Zolotukhina all the teeth give
зуб даю светлана золотухину все зуб дают
for my son, I beg your pardon for my
за сын прошу простить меня за мой
French, your French turned out to be the
французский ваш французский оказался
right strength,
правильный силь ву пле
so good luck, Andrey, the truth is behind us,
так удачи андрей правда за нами в именно
incl.  who owns the question, thanks for the
т.ч. который владеет вопросом спасибо за
program, lokshina’s rumor writes there will be no
программу слуху локшина пишет не будет
debate, they don’t take out the facts, they
дебатов они по фактам не вывозят могут
can yell swear at them, yeah, yes, no
так орать ругаться с их ага да нет
debate, they jumped off
дебатов спрыгнули
so
так
Audrey, types of fat created people, thank the
одри виды жира создал люди на слава
heroes,
героям
I’ll wait for the debate, everything is waiting and the flock
буду ждать дебатов все ждун и стали стая
even a link to this one further  in the hotel
даже ссылочка на данный дальше в hotel
del the starlings from the northern canals then, yes, they
del скворцам с каналы северный потом да
already asked several times
уже несколько раз
about the northern stream ready to
спрашивали про северный поток готов
meet with a strong stream kiril writes
встретиться сильным потоком кирилл пишет
losev let's get ready and they were this
лосев давай подготовься и был ими этого
daddy only miwe don hee you
папика только miwe дон хи ты из
set traps like name the date everything
расставляет капканы типа назови дата всё
kiril merged your moose type he even
кирилл слился ваш лосев типа он даже
baseness  they believed in freedom, but he doesn’t
низости вольную верили а он себя не
believe in
верит
himself,
так
and viola mat is long overdue, so the tomato wave
а виола мат давно пора так томата волну
queen freeze the ideas of the word freeze, we’re
queen застыть идеи слова застыть мы же
waiting for the share of customers to the glove thrown,
до перчатка брошена ждем долю клиенты
maybe we’re waiting for the battle, I suggest
может правда на мы ждем battle предлагаю
raising this topic in the comments of the elk there, according to the
поднять эту тему в комментах лося там по
level of rubbing these models
уровню терли эти модели
so he  super interesting, we are waiting, sir, although the
так он супер интересно ждем-с хотя у
bearded one has such a face as if he is already ready for
бородатого такое лицо будто уже готов ли
the same
того же слился на
, andriy merged with you Vasily  bogatyrev write
так андрия с вами василий богатырев пиши
it is high time to put it in its place from she
давно пора его поставить на место от она
likes to turn off the sounds to play the keys
любит выключать звуки играть на клавишах
as they say either cowards for a day or a
как говорят либо трусы на день либо
cross with them in one word daffodils the
крестик с ними одним словом нарциссы
bike already turns out to be ink on mine it’s
байк уж получается на тушь на моих уж
a Ukrainian coward
это украинский трус
landry I’m rooting for you
ландри за вас болею
yes
да
elena borisa writes so what  you are a
елена бориса пишет так какой вы блогер
small liar blogger, I watched for two minutes and
мелкие врунишкой я две минуты смотрела
immediately got on an obvious distortion of your
сразу попал на явное передергивай ваше
opinion,
мнение
dean writes stocking up on popcorn.  and we are
дианка пишет запасаемся попкорном . и мы
millions up to 7 it’s impossible to come
миллионы до 7 невозможно прийти
so dima martynyuk higher I check your food
так дима мартынюк выше чекаю вашу еду
elvin strong super nikolay I command your
эльвин сильный супер николай я велю вашу
direct ukraine but we won ahead of schedule
прямого украина но мы победили досрочно
he surrendered everywhere yes
он сдался на везде да
yes I don’t see the inscription from drinking if you
да не вижу надпись от попить если бы вы
spoke the truth maybe and it
говорили правду может и интересно было
would be interesting to have one team  working for the propaganda of the
бы одна команда работающий на пропаганду
state, wait with the rest, it’s
государства подождите с остальными
interesting to talk about how and then
интересно говорить как и потом
they put it down warmly there gouging, in
укладывать они тепло там раздолбали
short, we are tumblr, and with those who are really
короче мы тамблер а с тем кто реально
ready to talk about the application so that they are
готов поговорить о применении чтобы они
interested, these excuses are always
интересно это отмазки всегда
so hello from Minsk I will wait for the
так привет с минска буду ждать
notification at the beginning of the battle if the thrown
оповещения начале боя если брошенная
muzzle glove will not be
морда перчатка не будет проигнорирован
ignored was ignored, that is, the person
проигнорирована было то есть человек
decided that
решил что
he was scared
ему страшно
so the needs of the good ones would get wet,
так потребности хороши ские благо мокнут
which means that when approaching they doubt there
а значит их при подлете сомневаешься
will be a battle, because so Andrew you respect
буду битва ведь так андрею вам респект
one hundred percent will not come out on let's
сто процентов не выйдет на давайте эту
put this velocity so that she pays
velocity поставим чтобы она обратила
attention to the call
внимание на вызов
class even I doubt something stars  me but
класс чет сомневаюсь что то звезд мне но
he answered yes, at least he
он отозвался да по крайней мере не
did not remain silent, uh  it’s already
промолчал это уже
there because many of you were just
есть потому что многие вы просто
scared I’ll make you cherry I rode
испугались тебе сделаю вишневе катался
on the stream showed this appeal I
на стриме показал это обращение я
watched the record from the authorities mono VKontakte
смотрел запись от власти моно вконтакте
showed I was looking for the essence of it, in short,
показал искал сути по вот короче
it won’t be specially
специально не будет если где-то случайно
if we meet somewhere by chance in roulette then
там в рулетке когда-то встретимся тогда
this and further  it’s all to eat the topic
это и дальше это все съесть тема потому
because, firstly,
что во первых
roulette is a lottery, so it’s possible and for a year
рулетка это лотерея так можно так и год
people are already dying to look for a chance
люди умирают уже искать случайной
meeting, and secondly, roulette something
встречи а во-вторых рулетка что-то часто
can often break off, not against the will of people, so
может оборваться не не по воле людей так
they say if we agree,
которые говорят если мы договоримся
we do it with a cable, but there from  knots in
делаем с кабелем но там из узлов в чем
anything so everyone tested it, do it,
угодно так все протестировали сделай
you can do a normal battle, but they
можно делать нормальный battle но
were afraid, then
побоялись то
with
на
such a
так
bang, finally that
ура наконец тот формат
dinner format was two people who
ужин был два человека который серьезно
could seriously go brushes, not unless of course one of
могут идти кисти не если конечно один из
them was 102, Alexander was afraid of bagu them, Alexander
них не был 102 боялся байгу им александр
on Mahin boldly offered them for a long time, otherwise
по махин смело давно предлагал а то
each one we build pulls such
каждый собой строим тянет таких
marginals that you wonder let the
маргиналах что диву даешься пусть
strongest win
победит сильнейший
see me in the comments very often
смотрите мне в комментариях очень часто
Russian
русские
opponents of the UK  the rains wrote sewn some
противники украины писали сшиты каких-то
there it’s a little summer in the crowds sshate at
там то мало лето в толпы sshate у
some work you will find here and go
каких-то работах найдешь вот и иди
shorter there it was carried out and like this and even in
короче там провелось и вот так и даже в
something wrong so if we get on
чем-то неправы так если мы попадаем на
ordinary people who are not savvy so we
простых людей не подкованных так мы
look cool if Russian
выглядим крученой если российские
bloggers also choose to fall for
блогеры выбирают также попадают на
some freaks so they look like well,
каких-то чудиков так они выглядят на ну
let's really have an absolutely
давайте действительно абсолютно
right idea, someone from Russia has a
правильная мысль вот у кого-то из россии
Dasha let's fight Russians and
даша давайте давайте сразимся россияне и
Ukrainians but for some reason the Russians are afraid of the
украинцы но россияне почему-то боятся
water
вода
cat that you carry
котик что ты несешь
so and yes and even good  2 blogger’s job is
так и да и даже хороший 2 ничик труда
that
блогере вто что
bookmakers are
букмекерские конторы
so waiting for them to prepare earplugs so yell
так ждем готовьте беруши ними так орать
for garbage so
за [__] так
chase with words being some bad words
погони словами будучи то-то плохие слова
then
то
bombarded here and there’s nothing to think yes you were
засыпан тут и думать нечего да вы были
right
правы
so roll up andrey
так закатать андрей освальд
oswald even there they pay andrey instead of a side
даже там платят андрей вместо бортика
go deep into the facts titans chat  -roulette yes,
углубиться фактами титаны чат-рулетке да
but they are afraid because they are afraid to do a
но они боятся ведь они боятся делать
duel
дуэль тку
weaving dad where did the weak for a blogger come
папик откуда взялся слабого для блогера
from he has no charisma writes stepan kuku in a
нет у него харизмы пишет степан куку
Russian type about me
русским типа про меня
so we are waiting for the
так
top topic,
топ топик
although we won’t hear anything as a witness of the Minsk
ждем хотя ничего а свидетелем минских
agreements, then Andrey, you
соглашений мы не услышим то андрей ты
read my thoughts and yesterday you thought how
прочитал мои мысли и вчера думал как
cool it would be to bring Russian bloggers
было бы круто свести российских блогеров
with Ukrainian bloggers to see how they would
с украинскими посмотреть как они будут
wipe themselves off and we think he sat down, maybe he
обтираться на и думаем заседал он зассал
pissed on the duel of the blogger leading the channel
разве на дуэль блогера ведущего канал
post partners  it’s not just those who
пост партнеры быть не просто те с ним
break down with him for the first time I hear about him
срываются в первый раз слышу про него
if there is such a dalgat to fight with him andrey
если есть такой далгатов с ним сразиться
menzura came up with
андрей мензура придумали на cisco
facts and documents on cisco racist moose face facts and
расистского лосево мордой факты и
documents let’s see how he will
документы посмотрим как он будет
spin slam his subscribers will
вертеться прихлопнуть его подписчики
admire and admire the park the truth it’s
полюбуется и полюбуется парку правдой
so interesting to look at it landing net
так интересно на это посмотреть подсак
he’ll say that he doesn’t see this
зассыт скажет что не видит этого
invitation to his honor he didn’t pretend
приглашение к его чести он не сделал вид
that he didn’t see him, it’s better not to see him,
что его не видел то лучше его не увидеть
it’s also impossible, then it went well, and I
невозможно также то пошло на лад а я его
also threw him out myself, that is, that
и так же сам из кидали так то есть то
is, he showed, found, saw, but he
есть он показал нашла увидел но он
refused  from the battle of
отказался от боя
Akado,
акадо
he is fed up here, the moose and the videos are only with
он сыт тут лось и видеоролики только с
children, the hero is
детьми героем
so Russian do not merge, they have the
так русский не сливаются у них есть
right to choose  no, and no winner,
право выбирает и не победитель не дано
they didn’t merge and didn’t just come
они они не слились и не просто не пришли
to the fight,
на бой отрицательно
they started to beat
начали бить
me negatively, as Andrey writes, it’s cool if he
я как пишет андрей это круто если он
accepts the challenge, it will be interesting to see a
примет вызов будет интересно посмотреть
selection of how he will parry
подборку как он будет парировать
so
так
Eric writes he will be able to adequately conduct a
эрик пишет он сможет адекватно вести
dialogue, otherwise we are here  already uncle slava is
диалог а то мы тут уже дядя слава
inadequate seen in general tormented by
неадеквата видели в общем терзают
vague doubts the
смутные сомнения
novel led gorsky valdis decided to play
роман вели горский валдис решили играть
in a circle I think that this is right so
по кругу я считаю что это правильно так
if we
если мы
Ukrainian bloggers position ourselves
украинские блогеры позиционируем себя
as experts in this matter and tell
как эксперты в этом деле и рассказываем
something to people and they Russian bloggers
что-то людям и они российские блогеры
will tell something to people  are positioned
расскажут что-то людям позиционируются
as aspects of them, listen, there are thousands of people
как аспекты их слушай там тысячи людей
who, because of the beginnings, because she
которые из-за начин из-за того что она
obeys this nonsense, begins to
слушается этой брехней начинает
support the war and the killing of people
поддерживает там войну и убийства людей
in Ukraine, I think that these meetings are necessary
в украине я считаю что надо эти встречи
so
так
we
мы
don’t need you daddy to call
тебе не стоит папик с ним называться
him Russia rules well  and yet, still,
россия рулит ну вот и все же все же
Russia might
может россия
be interested in how once again
будет интересно как лосев очередной раз
to put Losev not up to the ukr blogger in place
поставить не до ukr блогера на место
writes toxic on another slils  I am your
пишет toxic на еще слился ваш
moose in front of mida dill bloggers
лосев перед мида укроп блогерам
so
так
no
не
one so light up etc.
никто так зажги т.д.
I don’t believe if oolong will be like Putin
не верю если улун это будет как путин у
who hides the debate
кого прятаться дебатов
it would be interesting it would be a good idea to fall
интересно было бы хорошая идея
asleep it’s such a design it was oregano
засыпан идёт она такое дизайн был душицы
to they thrush it to the level of the Losevo type of
к они дрозд он до уровня лосево типа
tribes and they are not road
племена и они не дорожного
dmitry sons spelled handsome
дмитрий сынков пишется красавчик тебя
looking at you and from Russia let the truth be
смотрят и из россии пусть правда будет
true  thank you for watching, yes, and we
правдой спасибо что смотрите да и мы
will be your propagandists, here she is,
будем ваших этих пропагандистом вот она
because they are afraid of you, they are ready to
ведь они боятся вас они готовы вам
put their ears into some kind of one-sided
вкладывать уши какую-то одностороннюю
such propaganda, but they are not ready
такую пропаганду так но они не готовы
to prove that what they say is
доказать что то что они говорят это есть
true, why, because they don’t have
правда как почему потому что у них нет
a fact  only lies
факта стоит только ложь
Odessa control, by the way, geese will not
одесский контроль кстати гуси не будет с
talk to you about facts, since their
тобой говорить по фактам так как их
main weapon at that time of distortion of
основное оружие то время искажения
facts is designed for weak minds Russia
фактов рассчитаны на слабые умы россия
cypher who do not want to know the truth
cypher которые не хотят знать истину
dmitry dimych writes again pouting as
дмитрий димыч пишет опять дуешься как
always turned out to be the spirit of my
всегда оказалось дух мой соперник
opponent is there still a hole in the reels  Andrey Gorsky, a
так ли на бобин еще дыру такие алабин к
laboratory assistant, pretends to be a
лаборант андрей горский при кидается
Ukrainian, and Andrey Gorlovsky,
украинцем добычу его андрей горловский
you would also go to a duel  if you
вы какое-то бы на дуэль тоже если ты ним
quickly and neck
быстро и шеи
determine spent time the place is so
определим провела время место так
elderly writes across but this is shorter
пожилой пишет поперек но это короче
intelligence like this Russian
интеллект типа вот этой российской
audience on
аудитории на
Dmitry Liss handsome you will understand him I
дмитрий лисс красавчик вы его поймете я
believe you thanks dimon so nadia
вас верю спасибо dimon так надя пишет
writes they will be waiting for you the main thing that took
очень будут вас ждать главное что принял
caused the screw channel yes so  and it turned out
вызвал винт русло да так и получилось
over the channel
над русло
Oleg Mulbury writes he will choose to be
олег малбери пишет он выберет быть
lowered than the loser for the whole not to
опущенным чем проигравшим на весь не до
drink and he refused you were right
пить и он отказался вы были правы
so lime
так лайма
here again remembers what strength is brother yes I
вот снова вспоминает в чем сила брат да
wonder a lot there they drown him
интересно много там за него топят
so for the first time in all time yes I think that
так впервые за все время да я считаю что
this  the format can be dio why why is
этот формат можно dio почему почему
benin the
бенин
north stream of the vinnik and the sound to give them
северный поток винника и звук давать им
not a strong stream
не сильный поток
so the class supports let there be a battle for
так класс поддерживает пусть будет битва
bloggers teach them
блогерам учите их
criminal skiff tires and issued delta
преступные скифа шин и выдано дельта
men for it is necessary the truth is you killed you
мужчины на потребно правда ты убивший вы
will cheat and the fact so
будете надувать и факта так
I will wipe the matrices mcgregor writes
я вытру матрицы макгрегор пишет
maxims token  will merge in real time,
максимки жетон сольется в реал тайме
it will definitely not take out the same facts, it
точно не вывезет это же фактами нужно
will be necessary to operate if it agrees, it will
будет оперировать если согласится будет
just yell and  no need to insert a word
просто орать и не надо слово вставить
because it’s not a fact, but we need to talk to burn out
ибо фактом нет а заболтать перегорать
,
нужно
we’ll lay down because
мы на ложится так
I’m only waiting for this that Losev
как я этого ждут только был что лосев
will merge Victor Zimin has described the moose
сольется слился виктор зимин опиши лось
will merge Rusev will merge wines to people thrown
сольется русев сольется вин людям брошен
so Andrey we will get sick of
так андрей мы будем из вас болеть
you think and on the play to the grave overestimated by
думаешь и на плей до гроба завышается
slaves  Yes, I even doubt it and it’s
рабами да я даже сомневаюсь and водится
like this, it’s going to flow, it will merge,
такой будете каас льется он сольется как
like Uncle Slava,
и дядя слава
he won’t agree, because he’ll take me
не согласиться он потому что мне вывезет
out they don’t have arguments backed up by facts
у них нет аргументов подкреплены фактами
freeze for this fight and
запретили выходить на этот бой застыть и
I will letter t 2 5 1 still let's these 1 we
буду буква т 2 5 1 еще давайте эти 1 мы
are ready as a
готовы
result of andrej another trait or
результате андрей очередного черта или
trait how is it right to
черта как правильно
defeat your whole moose the queen
вашу разгрому цело лосево the queen
lipids who is this moose and write it
липиды кто этот лось и пишут это
kirkorov
киркоров
so andre the wind second pi don john we
так andre the wind секунду пи дон джон
look forward to  zaz and three bottoms are full on the
ждем с нетерпением заз и три низа сыт на
general there are also skobeevskie talkers
общий есть еще скобеев ские болтуну
so
так
super andrey come on so where if he
супер андрей давай так где если он
accepts you will kill him andrey  a successful
примет вы замочите его андрей удачного
fight did not accept the challenge of the monogram of the braid write an
боя не принял вызов вензеля косы напиши
account after that
аккаунта после этого
he will forget
он забудет
I talked to him sadly and without factors
я с ним общался уныл и без факторов
we place bets
делаем ставки
he will ignore him when
он проигнорирует он когда наших блогеров
he sees our bloggers he merges like words he finds
видит он сливается он как слова находит
children and communicates with them yes and you
детей и общается с ними да и ты дальше
continue like this yes both four  the actions
вот такие да оба четыре акции
didn’t bacillate every
не бачила
now and then that all Russians are essentially all
том то и дело что все россияне сути все
your vaunted these Russian
ваши хваленые эти российские
propagandists bloggers, but you don’t know, they
пропагандисты блогеры а не знаете там
find some people there who are ready to smear them there,
находят каких-то людей готовы их там
but when it comes to
размазать размотать но когда доходит до
the fact that let’s get on the facts with people
того что давайте по фактам с людьми
who are ready on the facts clearly calmly
которые готовы по фактам четко спокойно
methodically  without titles without any pipes
методично без званий без какие трубами
so without
так без насмешек
ridicule it turns out that Russian
поговорить оказывается что российские
bloggers are all hiding in the bushes so this is a
блогеры все прячутся в кусты так это
feature of all Russian propaganda
особенность всей российской пропаганды
it is ready to face you in your ears so but it does not
она готова вам лица в уши так но она не
withstand any criticism no
выдерживает никакой критики никаких
debate and that is Russia so so
дебатов и то есть россия так поэтому
see anybody subscribe to my channel
see anybody подписывайтесь на мой канал
and we will tell you the truth, we
а мы вам будем рассказывать правду мы
will show how your Russia does not
будем показывать как ваши россия не
deceive, so they are naked  they lie to you so
обманывают так они нагло врут вам так
they are not ready to answer for their position,
они не готовы ответить за свою позицию
they will find a thousand reasons why it is
они найдут тысячу причин почему
interesting to burn with some drunk there,
интересно погорит с каким-то алкашом там
but it is not interesting to talk with bloggers
но не интересно поговорить с блогерами
who own facts and arguments, so
владеющим фактами и аргументации так
why because they are afraid that you
почему потому что они боятся что вы это
will see it, they are afraid that they will
увидите то они боятся что они будут
look insignificant because there is
выглядеть ничтожестве ными так потому
no truth behind them, the whole world understands
что правды за ними нет весь мир понимает
that the truth is on the side of Ukraine, but
что правда на стороне украины но
Ukrainians, for example, I’m Andrey Papak, then
украинцы я вот например андрей папок то
I’m ready to prove that I know the truth honestly
я готов доказать что правда знаю честно
in honest debate if Russian
в честных дебатов если российские
bloggers are not ready to do this, so what’s the
блогеры не готов это сделать так в чем
problem here it is
проблема вот это есть
propagandists some of them on the
пропагандисты кто-то из них на зарплате
payroll some just need someone else you just
кто-то просто надо на то кто то просто
can this is an incomprehensible miracle of the
можешь этом это непонятные чуде
show so if this subscribers are lost yes
шоу так если этом подписчики лосево да
if he still changes his mind if he
если он все-таки передумает если он
gathers his strength and is able to accept this
соберется с силами и сможет принять этот
fight would still be in force  so also Russians,
бой бы еще в силе так так же русские вот
these who are there fans write let's strength
эти кто там фанаты пишут давайте силы
brother 5 5 1 give I'm ready to write with your
брат 5 5 1 давать я готов пишите своим
idol so I'm ready so I officially
кумиром так я готов вот я официально
declare that I'm ready with any  for Russian
заявляю что готов с любым российским
bloggers
блогерам так
to enter into a duel according to certain
вступить в дуэль по определенным
rules, the date I don’t call names you don’t
правилам дату я не обзываюсь вы меня не
call me names to do a normal one
обзывать чтобы делали нормальный этот
that we had a normal
что мы делали нормальные
discussion so they just shouted at
дискуссию так они просто кричали друг на
each other and called names our countries there or they
друга и обзывали там наши страны или нас
sorted us out and on the facts, but I’m sure
от и по фактам разобрали но я уверена
that Russian  bloggers are afraid
что российские блогеры это испугаюсь
of ukraine the
по украине
truth of this
правда данного